- Ah, Xmas season is upon us.
Secure the perimeter!
Razor lights in place?
- Roger!
- Then, stand back!
Intruder alert.
- Santa's not getting
past that! No way!
Unless he knocks it down or something.
- Hey, robot.
- Someone left a card
in your stocking.
- That's weird.
Normally, I get mail
delivered to my ass.
"I know what you
did next Xmas!"?
Okay... Random!
- I wonder what
you will have done
and who could possibly
will have known about it.
- Eh, I do a lot of stuff. I'm
probably doing something right now.
- Who's ready for their very
first animated holiday special?
- Hooray!
- So fun!
-Whatever.
- Ooh! Wait for me. I love
having other kids around.
This year's rerun
of There's a Holiday for Everyone
is brought to you by...
Mom's Old Fashioned
Blood Remover.
Now in oatmeal spice.
- And that holiday is Xmas.
Hey,
kids, any chance
y'all wanna remix
this holiday special,
and hear the dope story
of Kwanzaabot instead?
- Or your favorite goofy
golem, Chanukah Zombie?
- No! Tell us about Santa!
- Again?
- Yes! Every year!
Oy...
The ancient tradition of Xmas
began in the year 2801,
when the Friendly Robot Company
developed a high-powered
mechanical Santa
capable of delivering over
five mega-presents per second.
Hey...
They tricked him out
with a pair of carbon-fiber Tims
and a chrome
naughty-nice sensor.
So he'd
know who deserved gifts
and who deserved
brutal punishment.
- Yo, that might've been the
first mistake right there.
But on Santa's very first delivery,
something went
tragically meshuggenah.
His naughty-nice
sensor malfunctioned.
Man, that's some
bleeped-up.
- Yay! Santa's here!
Oh! Oh my!
Oh, thank you.
- I'm sorry, kids.
I never wanted you to
know Santa was real.
- Yuletide news, everyone!
I know how to fix Santa!
I just need to sneak up on him
and reverse the polarity
of his naughty-nice sensor.
- But Santa is always on guard
against attacks. Just like me.
Hii-yah!
- Ow!
- You'll never be able
to sneak up on him.
- Not through space, no,
but through time, probably.
You see, Santa is only prepared
for an attack from the present.
So I've been souping
up my old time machine.
- Where is it?
- The question is when is it?
And the answer is right about...
now!
- It's so amazing.
I don't even care
that it's on my foot.
- I've installed a manual
transmission with a reverse gear,
so it can now go backward
in time as well as forward.
Hooray...
- My plan is to back
up to the year 2801,
when things first went wrong,
and materialize behind Santa
as he exits this very fireplace.
- Did this building
even exist in 2801?
- Yeah, but back then, it
was some kinda meat market,
where butchers would hook
up and grind their sausages.
- Yes, anyway, once there,
I'll quickly
reverse the polarity
of Santa's naughty-nice sensor,
then return to the present.
Problem solved.
- Um, Professor, isn't it
risky to go back in time
and change history?
- Oh my, yes.
But I'll go alone to
minimize the chance
of anyone becoming
their own grandfather.
- These things happen.
- No, they don't.
- Next time you see me, Santa
will have been good again!
Ta-ta!
Uh, just a couple of
centuries straight backwards.
Damn it! I backed over Mrs.
McGillicuddy's time cat!
Clutch, shift, and...
away we go!
Ho-ho-hot!
Cookie.
Cookie!
Just shift into forward and...
Whoa!
Oh, bother. I shifted
into reverse by accident.
I guess I'll have to take her
around by the scenic route.
Ah, here comes the
Big Backwards Bang.
Ow! I'm being crushed
by all the matter that
ever was.
- And here we are, the future!
Ee-eye!
- How'd it go?
- Not a hitch!
I fixed Santa!
- It'll be my first happy Xmas
since I got frozen and
never saw my family again!
- Now, hold on!
Xmas isn't for a week.
Until then, we got
nonstop busy work.
- Oh fuff. Let's
stop pretending
we do anything around here.
Everyone, take the week off,
and be with your
so-called loved ones.
Really?
- I forgot I had loved ones!
It's a human resources miracle!
- Uncle Fry, I hope
you'll join me and Cubert
at my chalet in the Bronx.
- Wait! My family's
hoping to meet Fry.
I mean, they met him before,
but he didn't make
much of an impression.
- I'll wear out my welcome at
one, and then go to the other.
- So, Bender...
- No.
- You and I are the only
ones with no family.
Maybe we could...
- No.
- Hang out?
- Oh. Hang out, you say?
Let me think that
over for a... No.
No. Oh, sorry.
Uh, I thought you
were still talking.
It's just you
and me, moldy sandwich man.
- Hello. Calculon acting.
- Hey, it's me! Your
extremely close friend Bender.
Wanna hang out?
- How did you get this number?
- I didn't! I'm just dialing
every number in order.
- Keep dialing.
This nuts bolts!
- Hey, Bender.
- Yes? I mean no!
- I brought dumpster nog...
And not the kind
for kids.
- Hm. What's in it?
- What's not in it?
You want nutmeg on that?
- Nutmeg? Gross!
Five golden rings!
Four something something,
three something else
Two no one cares,
and a partridge
Drowned in our nog!
- Whoof! This stuff is strong!
Hey, how many glasses
have we hadded?
- None. This is
just from the fumes.
- Aw, it's not fair!
Everyone else gets to have
fun with their stupid family.
- My species dies
when we reproduce.
So if I had a
family, I'd be dead.
Does anyone even care about that?
- I sure don't.
- If you ask me, "good"
Santa is ruining Xmas.
I'd like to give him such
a snipping.
- Ooh, I'd bend him a new one!
But he's not here right now!
- But, he has was been here.
Every Xmas, he shows
up in the fire hole.
- We could drunk
drive the time machine
to last Xmas and kidnap him!
Then, he won't be able to
deliver presents this Xmas!
- And our stupid friends'
holiday will be ruined!
Wait. Is kidnapping
Santa a good idea,
or does it just seem like a good
idea because we're intoximated?
It's a good idea.
Whee!
Set course for last Xmas!
Jingle bells, Zoidberg
smells just like rotten eggs
I'm
immortalized in song.
Cookie?
- And here we are, last Xmas.
Get him!
- Bite my glittering
festive ass!
Unhand me, you
naughty boys!
- Shove him in the
old meat locker!
- We have an old meat locker?
Silent night
Holy night
- Oh, boy. Hey, boy.
- Try spreading joy
now, you big Xmas ham.
- We're geniuses!
- I'm geniuses!
Do the Bender!
- You know, Zoidberg,
you're only half as bad
as I thought you were.
That means a lot.
Uh-oh.
We woke the meat up.
- What do we do?
- The time machine!
Good idea!
- Get ready to sleep
in heavenly peace!
Ho, ho...
Whoa!
Ooh... Ah...
Ooh...
- He's dead. We
killed Santa Claus.
- Uh... You killed Santy Claus.
- Uh... Robot?
- This was supposed to
be a fun kidnapping!
What do we do now?
- We gotta get rid of the body.
That's usually pretty fun.
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke! Stroke!
Stroke!
- Oops.
Oops.
Ow!
- Okay. Now, we just add some
extra weight to sink the corpse.
- It's not working!
Still nothing!
Why! Won't! You! Sink!?
Ah!
Hands up, boat bags.
- What's with the
bloated floater?
I admit it! We
murd...
- Uh, just, uh, dumping
some toxic waste, officers.
- Huh. Guess you gotta
put it somewhere.
- Carry on, night dumpers.
- Dwight, it's time to teach you
the Conrad holiday turducken recipe.
Cooked in alphabetical order.
- Alrighty then.
We gonna start with the
chicken, then duck, and then...
Let me see
now. Now the E and the F...
Husband! We
using flamingo this year?
- At $20 a pound!?
No, thank you.
- It's not working!
- Flush harder!
- I'm flushing as hard as
I can! Got any other ideas,
Mr.
I'm-So-Great-At-Hiding-Corpses?
- Well, at least I have
ideas! What do you suggest?
- Hm... We could
try an acid bath.
- That does sound
relaxing, but...
- No! We'll dissolve
Santa's body!
Professor has some acid
upstairs in his lab.
I'll go fill this trash bag.
Oops!
- Remind me, is this
the ground floor?
- Behold, my family's
traditional Yuletide feast.
Turdolphin!
It's fresh turtle cooked
inside a fermented dolphin.
- Wow. Soon, it's gonna
be barf inside a vomit.
- Dad. Shh! Keep the
truth to yourself.
- Which part smells
like whale butt?
- Ooh, that would be the gravy.
You ruined everything!
You're the one who
wanted to kidnap Santa!
- Oh, yeah? Well,
you enabled me,
so shut up and keep pushing
him into the meat grinder!
- Bender, look! It's working!
Wait. Where's my claw?
- Gather round,
relatives, as I cook up
turducken a la Farnsworth
with this 3D poultry printer.
- As long as it's got three
dimensions, I'll eat it.
- We start with liquid chicken.
Then, some duck filament.
And finally, a
whole fresh turkey.
I printed this one out earlier.
- Oh, man. I need to head out
if I'm gonna make it to Leela's.
Do you have any skis?
- No, but I can print some.
- How are we making turducken?
There's nothing in the refrigerator.
- Eh, that fridge doesn't work.
We use it as a spare bedroom.
- We serve fresh
turducken, Leela.
They roam the
sewers in huge flocks.
- Are they hard to catch?
- Oh, no.
They crave death.
- Hey! Sorry I'm late.
I got hungry and ate my skis.
- Fry, you made it!
You remember my
parents and my grandma?
Ah, yes. The rose of the sewers.
Mwah!
- Leela, if you don't marry him,
I will.
- So, uh, where's
Bender and Zoidberg?
- What? I figured they were
with you. Or something.
They're probably
relaxing by the fire.
- The only rational
option is to eat Santa.
Right? Right!?
- I don't know!
Oh, this is a
nightmare before Xmas.
I wish we'd never
become friends!
- We're not friends!
And we never were!
- But we danced. And murdered.
- I'll do the carving. You want
white Christmas or dark Christmas?
Surprise!
- Bah humbug!
- Nobody's home! Leave
a message at the beep.
Beep!
- Open up or we'll carol!
Uh, Bender!
We have company!
Uh, just a
sec! I'm tidying up.
Hii-yah!
- Come in, come in!
Everything's normal.
- Merry Xmas, you guys.
- We didn't know you hadn't
been invited anywhere.
- We came as soon as we
realized what losers you are.
- Uh, punch?
- Nah, I'll just have a beer.
- Who's hungry? We all brought
our families' unique
holiday dishes.
- Turducken!
- Turdolphin!
- Huh.
- How thoughtful of you all to
drop this disturbing food off,
and then be immediately
on your way. Goodbye!
- Dinner's served!
Isn't that pretty? It
looks like a magazine.
- Bender, since when
do you have three legs?
- Uh, uh, th-this one's a spare.
In case I break
down on the highway.
- And why is it
wearing a snow boot?
- Finally, an
old-time happy Xmas,
with presents for everyone!
I'm hoping
for Batman underpants.
- Santa should be
here any minute now.
- The guilt is too
much! I confess!
Santa won't...
- What's that? Who's jingling!?
- Ah, here he comes!
- Yay! It's good Santa!
- Indeed, because I fixed him.
- Santa seems less
dead than we thought.
Ooh...
I don't understand. He's still evil!
I personally went back in time
and reversed his
naughty-nice sensor!
Uh-oh.
- What you do, old man?
Oh, I've made a complete Fry of myself.
You see, Santa's sensor
was exactly like the one
on this punch bowl.
When he was first built,
it was in the correct position.
But when I went back in
time, I flipped it around.
Me! Oh, lordy-loo.
I'm the one who made Santa evil.
You monster!
You've all
been very naughty!
Especially you, Mandy.
- I'm sorry I forgot
to feed the hamster!
- Arm yourselves!
Cookie?
- And here we are, last Xmas.
Get him!
- Bite my glittering
festive ass.
Unhand me, you
naughty boys.
Who are those handsome guys,
and what are they
doing to poor Santa?
- That's us, you idiot.
You didn't take us to last Xmas.
You took us to next
Xmas! Meaning this Xmas!
- Damn it, Bender. I'm a doctor,
not a time machine guy!
I think I speak for everyone when I say,
uh-whuh?
- I can't hold it in anymore!
- We kidnapped and
murdered Santa!
- Oh.
- We didn't mean to, but still!
- Stop blubbering, you bloobs!
You're heroes!
What-roes?
- The professor
set Santa to kill!
You saved all
19 of us!
- We're heroes?
- Damn right, we are!
Do the Bender! Do
the Bender! Do the Bender!
Aw, Bender!
You and Zoidberg
are friends now?
That's so cute.
- Uh, absolutely not!
You're all having a
mass hallucination!
- So, what happened to Santa?
- You're drinking out of him.
- There's one thing I
still don't understand.
Which one of you meatbags
wrote the creepy notes?
'Twas I!
I sent the notes
from the future!
- Because I murdered you?
- No! Because I knew
what you did next Xmas.
You became friends
with Zoidberg!
So I'm blackmailing you!
- No... No!
You take Amy's Venmo?
- Sure.
- Hey!
Cookie!
- Yo, Santa Bot!
I'ma drop my Futurama
Xmas list for 3023.
Y'all ready for this?
I'm about to get nice.
Kwanzaabot. Yeah.